[
    {
      "cell_ids": [
        6
      ],
      "question": "What are the unique rating values in the dataset?",
      "answer": "[4.  5.  3.  2.  1.  4.5 3.5 2.5 0.5 1.5]",
       "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
      "cell_ids": [
        8
      ],
      "question": "What are the names of the columns in the `movies` dataframe?",
      "answer": "movieId, title and genres",
       "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
      "cell_ids": [
        11
      ],
       "question": "What does the `partial_movieId` column represent?",
           "answer": "It represents the index of each movie, starting from 1 and increasing by one for each unique movie id.",
      "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              14
          ],
          "question": "How is the data split into training and testing sets in this notebook?",
           "answer": "The data is split using a 70/30 ratio by randomly sampling the indices",
          "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              17
          ],
          "question": "What is the shape of the rating matrix that is generated?",
           "answer": "The rating matrix shape is based on the max user id, and max partial_movie_id",
          "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              20
          ],
          "question": "What is the purpose of the `plot_learning_curve` method?",
           "answer": "To plot the training and testing mean squared error (MSE) over iterations to see how the model is converging.",
          "task": "Dashboard Summary",
          "skill": "Interactive Visualization"
      },
     {
          "cell_ids": [
              22
          ],
          "question": "What is the purpose of the `get_recommendation` function?",
           "answer": "It gets a list of movies (not rated yet) to be recommended to a given user.",
           "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
      },
       {
          "cell_ids": [
              26
          ],
          "question": "What method is used to train the MatrixFactorization model?",
           "answer": "Stochastic Gradient Descent (SGD)",
           "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
      },
      {
           "cell_ids": [
              28
          ],
         "question": "What do the top 5 recommendation generated for user id 1 shows?",
           "answer": "The recommendation shows high rating partial_movie_id for a given user.",
           "task": "Recommendation Systems",
          "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
      },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              30
          ],
          "question": "What does `get_title` method do?",
           "answer": "It returns the title of a movie, using movie id",
             "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      }
  ]